[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service is defined as 'virtual machines inside AWS'?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail",
        "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to run and manage docker containers at scale?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 Container Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service provides autoscaling groups, load balancers, EC2 instances, and allows developer to only have to focus on their code?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Beanstalk"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to upload your code to the cloud and control when it executes, not worrying about underlying physical or virtual machines or OSs?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "Lambda", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lambda"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to use a Virtual Private Server (VPS)?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service provisions a server, gives you a fixed ip address, rdp (windows) or ssh (linux) login shell access, and has its own management console?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service is thought of as 'a watered down version of EC2?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service gives you batch computing in the cloud?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "Batch", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Batch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you object based storage in the cloud based on 'buckets'?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you network attached storage and can mount these to multiple EC2 instances?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic File System (EFS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you data archival?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glacier"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you a way to bring large amounts of data into AWS and is used for TB sized transfers instead of using broadband or wireless?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service is a virtual appliance/machine that you install in your data center that replicates data into S3?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Storage Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Aurora, and Oracle databases as a managed service?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["RDS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you a NoSQL database as a managed service?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you a way of caching commonly queried data from your database?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elasticache"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you data warehousing or business intelligence?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Red Shift"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you tracking service allowing you to track your applications as you migrate them to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Migration Hub"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service integrates with other services within the migration framework to help you keep track of application and database migration activity and also has a visualization of all migration activity?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Migration Hub"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you an automated set of tools which detect what applications you have and what their dependencies are?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application Discovery Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you a way of tracking application dependencies?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application Discovery Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you an easy way to migrate your databases from on-premise to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Database Migration Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you a way to migrate virtual and physical servers from on-premise to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Server Migration Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service is used for migrating large amounts of data to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a virtual data center?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service is Amazon's Content Delivery Network (CDN)?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service allows you to store content closer to users around the globe using Edge Locations?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service is Amazon's DNS service?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Route 53"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a way of creating APIs for other services to talk to?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["API Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a way of running a dedicated line from your on-premise data center to your AWS VPC?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Direct Connect"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool gives you a way of getting a group of developers working together to 'project manage' their code?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Star"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool contains a delivery tool chain?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Star"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool provides a source control service where you can store your private git repositories?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Commit"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool allows you to compile your code, run tests, and produce software packages that are ready to deploy?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Build"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool automates application code deployment to your EC2 instances or on-premise instances, as well as to your lambda functions?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Deploy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool provides a continuous delivery service, where you can model, visualize, and automate the steps required to release your software?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool is used to deploy and analyze your serverless application code and has request tracing to help find issues and performance bottlenecks?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["X-Ray"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool gives you an IDE to develop code within the AWS console?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cloud9"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool provides you with a monitoring service for your AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you a way of scripting infrastructure and deployment of infrastructure?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFormation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you a way to turn infrastructure into code?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFormation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used to log changes to you AWS environment and stores its records for one week?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool monitors the configuration of your entire AWS environment?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Config"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool has point-in-time snapshots of your AWS environment and visualizes your AWS environment over time past through present?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Config"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool uses both Chef and Puppet to automate your environments and the configuration of your environments?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["OpsWorks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool manages a catelog of your account resources that are approved for use in your AWS account?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Service Catalog"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used for governance and compliance requirements for your AQS account?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Service Catalog"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you an interface for managing your AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used for EC2 for things like patch maintenance?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool would you use to install a patch across thousands of EC2 instances all at once?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you advice around security, cost optimization, performance, and fault tolerance?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Trusted Advisor"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool lets AWS manage your EC2 instances, auto-scaling, load balancers, etc?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Managed Services"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service transcodes videos so they appear correctly across all device types?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Transcoder"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is a file based video transcoding service?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaConvert"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is live video processing service?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaLive"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service prepares and protects videos for transfer over the internet?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaPackage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is a storage service that's optimized for video?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaStore"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service allows targeted advertising in video streams?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaTailor"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service makes it easy for developers to use deep learning (neaural networks) when coding their applications?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service does sentiment analysis of your data?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Comprehend"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is an artificially aware camera that can figure out what it's looking at using deep learning?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["DeepLens"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is service that powers Alexa?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service provides an artificially intelligent chat capability?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is a less sophisticated 'learning' tool than deep learning that uses data set analysis to predict outcome when new data sets are applied to it?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Machine Learning"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is the service that Amazon uses to recommend new products to its users?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Machine Learning"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service takes text and turns it into speech?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Polly"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service provides video and image contect recognition?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Rekognition"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is Amazon's machine translation service which translates one language into another?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Translate"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service automates speech recognition to produce transcription of video audio?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Transcribe"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service allows you to run SQL queries against data in your S3 buckets?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Athena"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is used for processing large anounts of data for big data solutions that uses many servers (running hadoop) to chop up your data for analysis?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EMR"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service manages all the server resources needed to build and deploy search indexes. All you have to do is upload your data to a search domain and start submitting requests?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudSearch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a popular open-source search and analytics engine for use cases such as log analytics, real-time application monitoring, and clickstream analytics?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elasticsearch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a way of ingesting large amounts of data into AWS , like social media feeds or tweets?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a way of ingesting video streams and do processing on the data?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Video Streams"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is Amazon's business intelligence tool, similar to Tableau?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["QuickSight"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service gives you a way of moving your data between different AWS services?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is used for Extract/Transform/Load types of analytics processing?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service enables you to manage access to AWS services and resources securely?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["IAM"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "80",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Once authenticated you can use this AWS security service to request temporary access to AWS resources like DynamoDB tables?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cognito"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "81",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service is an authentication service that gives temporary access to applications such as mobile apps and web apps?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cognito"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "82",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service monitors for malicious activity on your AWS account?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["GuardDuty"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "83",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service is an agent you install on your virtual machines or EC2 instances and then run tests on the instances such as security vulnerability tests; these tests can be scheduled?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Inspector"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "84",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service generates reports giving severity list of vulnerabilities in your EC2 instances?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Inspector"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "85",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service scans your S3 buckets and looks for personal identifiable information (PII)?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Macie"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service gives you a way to manage your SSL certificates?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Certificate Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "87",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service gives you your SSL certificates for free if you register your domain through Route 53?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Certificate Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service is a hardware security module (HSM) or dedicated hardware used to store your keys?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudHSM"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "89",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service gives you a way of integrating your Microsoft Active Directory services with your AWS services?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Directory Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service is like a layer 7 firewall which stops cross-site scripting, sql injection and looks at the application layer to detect malicious user behavior?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["WAF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service do you get by default when using CloudFront, load balancers, and Route 53?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Shield"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "92",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What AWS security services give you DDoS mitigation?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Shield", "Advanced Shield"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service gives you a dedicated 24x7 team to help you prevent DDoS attacks?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Advanced Shield"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you are attacked by a DDoS attack and you are using which AWS security service will Amazon then not charge you for your account activity related to the DDoS attack?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Advanced Shield"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "95",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service is used for audit and compliance; is a portal to download and access AWS compliance reports?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Artifact"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS security service can be used to manage compliance agreements and you can use it to download SOC controls reports or Payment Card Industry reports?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "Cognito", "GuardDuty", "Inspector", "Macie", "Certificate Manager", "CloudHSM", "Directory Service", "WAF", "Shield", "Advanced Shield", "Artifact"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Artifact"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "97",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS mobile service is a mobile management console that helps you use the AWS SDK to connect your mobile apps to your AWS back-end?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Mobile Hub"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "98",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS mobile service is a way of using targeted push notifications to drive mobile engagement?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Pinpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS mobile service updates data in web and mobile applications in real time and updates data for offline users as soon as they reconnect?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS AppSync"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS mobile service gives you a way of testing your apps on real live devices?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Device Farm"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS mobile service gives you an analytics service for mobile?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Mobile Analytics"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS AR/VR service is used for AR and VR application design and allows you to use a common set of tools to create these environments?",
      "answers": ["Mobile Hub", "Sumerian", "Pinpoint", "AWS AppSync", "Device Farm", "Mobile Analytics"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Sumerian"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS application integration service gives you a way of managing your Lambda functions by using steps to move through them?",
      "answers": ["Step Functions", "Amazon MQ", "SNS", "SQS", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Step Functions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS application integration service gives you a way of passing data through message queues?",
      "answers": ["Step Functions", "Amazon MQ", "SNS", "SQS", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon MQ"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS application integration service is a notification service used with alarms to send notification of alarm trigger?",
      "answers": ["Step Functions", "Amazon MQ", "SNS", "SQS", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["SNS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS application integration service is a way of decoupling your infrastructure through queues?",
      "answers": ["Step Functions", "Amazon MQ", "SNS", "SQS", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS application integration service is a way of managing a workflow such as package order processing in a warehouse?",
      "answers": ["Step Functions", "Amazon MQ", "SNS", "SQS", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["SWF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS customer engagement service is a contact center as a service which can have dynamic, periodic, and natural customer engagement at any scale?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Connect", "Simple Email Service", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Connect"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS customer engagement service is a way of sending large amounts of email?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Connect", "Simple Email Service", "SWF"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Simple Email Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "110",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS business productivity service can be used to start your meeting by dialing into a meeting room?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Chime", "Work Docs", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Alexa for Business"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "111",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS business productivity service is a video conferencing service?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Chime", "Work Docs", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Chime"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "112",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS business productivity service is like a dropbox service for AWS that gives you a way of securely storing your work related documents?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Chime", "Work Docs", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Work Docs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "113",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS business productivity service is Amazon's version of Office 365 and gives you a way of using your email through Amazon similar to gmail?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Chime", "Work Docs", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Work Mail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "114",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS desktop and app streaming service is a VDI solution that gives you a way of running the desktop OS in the AWS cloud?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Workspaces", "AppStream 2.0", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Workspaces"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "115",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS desktop and app streaming service gives you a way of running desktop apps in the cloud and streaming its visuals to your user device, similar to Citrix?",
      "answers": ["Alexa for Business", "Workspaces", "AppStream 2.0", "Work Mail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AppStream 2.0"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "116",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS internet of things service gives you a way for devices to send sensor information to AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["IoT", "IoT Device Management", "Amazon FreeRTOS", "Greengrass"],
      "correctAnswer": ["IoT"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "117",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS internet of things service gives you a way to manage iOT devices at scale?",
      "answers": ["IoT", "IoT Device Management", "Amazon FreeRTOS", "Greengrass"],
      "correctAnswer": ["IoT Device Management"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "118",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS internet of things service gives you an operating system for your microcontrollers?",
      "answers": ["IoT", "IoT Device Management", "Amazon FreeRTOS", "Greengrass"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon FreeRTOS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "119",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS internet of things service is software that lets you run local compute messaging, data caching, sync, and machine learning interface capabilities for connected devices?",
      "answers": ["IoT", "IoT Device Management", "Amazon FreeRTOS", "Greengrass"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Greengrass"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "120",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS game development service is a service to help you build games in the AWS cloud?",
      "answers": ["IoT", "IoT Device Management", "Amazon FreeRTOS", "Greengrass", "GameLift"],
      "correctAnswer": ["GameLift"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "121",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Company salespeople upload their sales figures daily. A Solutions Architect needs a durable storage solution for these documents that also protects against users accidentally deleting important documents. Which action will protect against unintended user actions?",
      "answers": ["Put the access key in an S3 bucket, and retrieve the access key on boot from the instance", "Pass the access key to the instances through instance user data", "Obtain the access key from a key server launched in a private subnet", "Create an IAM role with permissions to access the table, and launch all instances with the new role"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an IAM role with permissions to access the table, and launch all instances with the new role"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "122",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company is developing a highly available web application using stateless web servers. Which services are suitable for storing session state data?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "DynamoDB", "Elastic Load Balancing", "ElastiCache", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["DynamoDB", "ElastiCache"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "123",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Company salespeople upload their sales figures daily. A Solutions Architect needs a durable storage solution for these documents that also protects against users accidentally deleting important documents. Which action will protect against unintended user actions?",
      "answers": ["Store data in an EBS volume and create snapshots once a week", "Store data in an S3 bucket and enable versioning", "Store data in two S3 buckets in different AWS regions", "Store data on EC2 instance storage"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store data in an S3 bucket and enable versioning"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "124",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application requires a highly available relational database with an initial storage capacity of 8 TB. The database will grow by 8 GB every day. To support expected traffic, at least eight read replicas will be required to handle database reads. Which option will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": ["DynamoDB", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Aurora", "Amazon Redshift"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Aurora"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "125",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A Solutions Architect is designing a critical business application with a relational database that runs on an EC2 instance. It requires a single EBS volume that can support up to 16,000 IOPS. Which Amazon EBS volume type can meet the performance requirements of this application?",
      "answers": ["EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD", "EBS Throughput Optimized HDD", "EBS General Purpose SSD", "EBS Cold HDD"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "126",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A web application allows customers to upload orders to an S3 bucket. The resulting Amazon S3 events trigger a Lambda function that inserts a message to an SQS queue. A single EC2 instance reads messages from the queue, processes them, and stores them in an DynamoDB table partitioned by unique order ID. Next month traffic is expected to increase by a factor of 10 and a Solutions Architect is reviewing the architecture for possible scaling problems. Which component is MOST likely to need re-architecting to be able to scale to accommodate the new traffic?",
      "answers": ["Lambda function", "SQS queue", "EC2 instance", "DynamoDB table"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instance"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "127",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application saves the logs to an S3 bucket. A user wants to keep the logs for one month for troubleshooting purposes, and then purge the logs. What feature will enable this?",
      "answers": ["Adding a bucket policy on the S3 bucket", "Configuring lifecycle configuration rules on the S3 bucket", "Creating an IAM policy for the S3 bucket", "Enabling CORS on the S3 bucket"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configuring lifecycle configuration rules on the S3 bucket"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "128",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on EC2 instances processes sensitive information stored on Amazon S3. The information is accessed over the Internet. The security team is concerned that the Internet connectivity to Amazon S3 is a security risk. Which solution will resolve the security concern?",
      "answers": ["Access the data through an Internet Gateway", "Access the data through a VPN connection", "Access the data through a NAT Gateway", "Access the data through a VPC endpoint for Amazon S3"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Access the data through a VPC endpoint for Amazon S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "129",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An organization is building an Amazon Redshift cluster in their shared services VPC. The cluster will host sensitive data. How can the organization control which networks can access the cluster?",
      "answers": ["Run the cluster in a different VPC and connect through VPC peering", "Create a database user inside the Amazon Redshift cluster only for users on the network", "Define a cluster security group for the cluster that allows access from the allowed networks", "Only allow access to networks that connect with the shared services network via VPN"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Define a cluster security group for the cluster that allows access from the allowed networks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "130",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A Solutions Architect is designing an online shopping application running in a VPC on EC2 instances behind an ELB Application Load Balancer. The instances run in an Auto Scaling group across multiple Availability Zones. The application tier must read and write data to a customer managed database cluster. There should be no access to the database from the Internet, but the cluster must be able to obtain software patches from the Internet. Which VPC design meets these requirements?",
      "answers": ["Public subnets for both the application tier and the database cluster", "Public subnets for the application tier, and private subnets for the database cluster", "Public subnets for the application tier and NAT Gateway, and private subnets for the database cluster", "Public subnets for the application tier, and private subnets for the database cluster and NAT Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Public subnets for the application tier and NAT Gateway, and private subnets for the database cluster"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "131",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service securely controls access to AWS services and resources?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "AWS Organizations", "Amazon Cognito", "AWS Directory Service", "AWS Single Sign-On"],
      "correctAnswer": ["IAM"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "132",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service gives you policy-based management for multiple AWS accounts?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "AWS Organizations", "Amazon Cognito", "AWS Directory Service", "AWS Single Sign-On"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Organizations"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "133",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service allows you to add user sign-up, sign-in, and access control to your web and mobile apps?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "AWS Organizations", "Amazon Cognito", "AWS Directory Service", "AWS Single Sign-On"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Cognito"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service gives you managed Microsoft Active Directory in the AWS cloud?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "AWS Organizations", "Amazon Cognito", "AWS Directory Service", "AWS Single Sign-On"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Directory Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service gives you the ability to centrally manage single sign-on (SSO) access to multiple AWS accounts and business applications?",
      "answers": ["IAM", "AWS Organizations", "Amazon Cognito", "AWS Directory Service", "AWS Single Sign-On"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Single Sign-On"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service gives you the ability to easily configure and manage Amazon EC2 and on-premise systems to apply OS patches, create secure system images, and configure secure operating systems?",
      "answers": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "AWS Shield", "AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service gives you managed DDoS protection service that safeguards web applications running on AWS?",
      "answers": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "AWS Shield", "AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Shield"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service protects your web applications from common web exploits ensuring availability and security?",
      "answers": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "AWS Shield", "AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service automates security assessments to help improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS?",
      "answers": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "AWS Shield", "AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Inspector"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service provisions a logically isolated section of AWS where you can launch AWS resources in a virtual network that you define?",
      "answers": ["Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "AWS Shield", "AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service enables governance, compliance, and operational/risk auditing of your AWS account?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service records and evaluates configurations of your AWS resources, enabling compliance auditing, security analysis, resource change tracking, and troubleshooting?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Config"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service monitors AWS cloud resources and your applications on AWS to collect metrics, monitor log files, set alarms, and automatically react to changes?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service provides intelligent threat detection and continuous monitoring to protect your AWS accounts and workloads?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon GuardDuty"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service captures information about the IP traffic going to and from network interfaces in your VPC, log data is stored using Amazon CloudWatch logs?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs"],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC Flow Logs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Security",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What security service is a security service that uses machine learning to automatically discover, classify, and protect sensitive data in AWS?",
      "answers": ["AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "Amazon GuardDuty", "VPC Flow Logs", "Amazon Macie"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Macie"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is IAM?",
      "answers": ["Allows you to manage users and their level of access to the AWS console", "Defines EC2 storage types", "Gives you control of billing alarms", "Gives you authority over combined billing"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Allows you to manage users and their level of access to the AWS console"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "IAM gives you which of the following?",
      "answers": ["Centralized control of your AWS account", "Granular permissions", "Identity federation (including Active Directory, Facebook, Linkedin, etc.)", "Use of Multifactor Authentication", "Billing alarms"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Centralized control of your AWS account", "Granular permissions", "Identity federation (including Active Directory, Facebook, Linkedin, etc.)", "Use of Multifactor Authentication"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "IAM gives you which of the following?",
      "answers": ["Shared access to your AWS account", "Provide temporary access for users/devices and services", "Setup password rotation policy", "Supports PCI DSS compliance", "Resource monitoring"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Shared access to your AWS account", "Provide temporary access for users/devices and services", "Setup password rotation policy", "Supports PCI DSS compliance"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM what is a user?",
      "answers": ["Permanent resource that access AWS resources", "A collection of users under one set of permissions", "A temporary entity (person or machine/software) in the IAM service", "A document that defines one or more permissions"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Permanent resource that access AWS resources"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM what is a group?",
      "answers": ["Permanent resource that access AWS resources", "A collection of users under one set of permissions", "A temporary entity (person or machine/software) in the IAM service", "A document that defines one or more permissions"],
      "correctAnswer": ["A collection of users under one set of permissions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM what is a role?",
      "answers": ["Permanent resource that access AWS resources", "A collection of users under one set of permissions", "A temporary entity (person or machine/software) in the IAM service", "A document that defines one or more permissions"],
      "correctAnswer": ["A temporary entity (person or machine/software) in the IAM service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM what is a policy?",
      "answers": ["Permanent resource that access AWS resources", "A collection of users under one set of permissions", "A temporary entity (person or machine/software) in the IAM service", "A document that defines one or more permissions"],
      "correctAnswer": ["A document that defines one or more permissions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "IAM is a _____ resource, not associated with any particular region?",
      "answers": ["global", "regional", "local", "specific"],
      "correctAnswer": ["global"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Your account number is embedded in what IAM property, which you can customize to an account alias?",
      "answers": ["IAM user sign-in link", "IAM root role", "IAM admin group", "Account owners policy document"],
      "correctAnswer": ["IAM user sign-in link"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which apps can you use as an MFA tool with IAM for iOS and Windows phones?",
      "answers": ["Google Authenticator", "Authenticator", "MFA App", "MFA Man"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Google Authenticator", "Authenticator"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which keys do you use to programatically use AWS services through the CLI and APIs?",
      "answers": ["Access Key ID", "Secret Access Key", "Root Access Key", "Admin Access Key"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Access Key ID", "Secret Access Key"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can use the Access Key ID and Secret Access Key to login to the AWS console?",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can use the Access Key ID and Secret Access Key for programatic access to AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM you use which feature to manage passwords?",
      "answers": ["Apply an IAM password policy", "Manage IAM resources", "Manage IAM users", "Manage IAM roles"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Apply an IAM password policy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "The IAM dashboard Security Tasks are which of these?",
      "answers": ["Activate MFA on your Root account", "Create individual IAM users", "Use groups to assign permissions", "Apply an IAM password policy", "Rotate your access keys", "Delete your access keys"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Activate MFA on your Root account", "Create individual IAM users", "Use groups to assign permissions", "Apply an IAM password policy", "Rotate your access keys"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM, _____ are a way to grant permissions to entities you trust?",
      "answers": ["Roles", "Policies", "Users", "Groups"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Roles"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "In IAM you can use roles to do which of these?",
      "answers": ["Allow an IAM user from another account to access resources in this account", "Allow application code running in an EC2 instance that needs to perform actions on AWS resources (like S3)", "Allow an AWS service that needs to act on resources in your account to provide its features", "Allow users from a corporate directory who use identity federation with SAML", "Allow users to create billing alarms"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Allow an IAM user from another account to access resources in this account", "Allow application code running in an EC2 instance that needs to perform actions on AWS resources (like S3)", "Allow an AWS service that needs to act on resources in your account to provide its features", "Allow users from a corporate directory who use identity federation with SAML"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM roles issue keys that are _____, making them a more secure way to grant access?",
      "answers": ["valid for short durations", "valid for extended durations", "valid for indefinite duration", "invalid for short durations"],
      "correctAnswer": ["valid for short durations"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Cloud Foundation",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service do you use to monitor billing through Billing Alarms using Billing Alerts?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "IAM", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "IAM consists of the following?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "Users", "Roles", "Groups", "Policy Documents"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Users", "Roles", "Groups", "Policy Documents"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM you can apply ______ to users, groups, and roles?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "Keys", "Passwords", "Policy Documents"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Policy Documents"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM policy documents are made up of ______ containing key: value pairs?",
      "answers": ["JSON", "JavaScript", "XML", "CSV"],
      "correctAnswer": ["JSON"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM new users have what level of permissions when they are first created?",
      "answers": ["no permissions", "admin permissions", "power user permissions", "root permissions"],
      "correctAnswer": ["no permissions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "In IAM new users are assigned what when they are first created?",
      "answers": ["Access Key ID", "Secret Access Key", "Admin Access Key", "Permissions Key"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Access Key ID", "Secret Access Key"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In IAM you can create and customize your own what?",
      "answers": ["Password rotation policy", "Secret Access Key", "Admin Access Key", "Permissions Key"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Password rotation policy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is an AWS region?",
      "answers": ["A region is an independent data center, located in different countries around the globe.", "A region is a geographical area that consists of different availability zones. Each region at least two Availability Zones.", "A region is a collection of Edge Locations available in specific countries.", "A region consists of different subsets of AWS technologies. For example the compute region consists of EC2, ECS, Lambda, etc."],
      "correctAnswer": ["A region is a geographical area that consists of different availability zones. Each region at least two Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "173",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What does an AWS Region consist of?",
      "answers": [
        "A console that gives you quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.",
        "A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.",
        "An independent collection of AWS computing resources in a defined geography.",
        "A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.",
        "A content distribution network, which is used to distribute content to users."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An independent collection of AWS computing resources in a defined geography."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "174",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which statement best describes Availability Zones?",
      "answers": [
        "Availability Zones are Content Distribution Networks.",
        "A restricted area designed specifically for creating Virtual Private Clouds.",
        "Two zones containing compute resources that are designed to automatically maintain synchronized copies of each other's&nbsp;data.",
        "Distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "175",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An AWS VPC is a component of which AWS service?",
      "answers": [
        "Global Infrastructure",
        "Databases Service",
        "Networking Service",
        "Compute Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Networking Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "176",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is a VPC?",
      "answers": [
        "Virtual Public Cloud",
        "Virtual Private Compute",
        "Virtual Private Cloud",
        "Virtual Private Compute"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Virtual Private Cloud"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "177",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service is specifically designed to run a developer's code on an infrastructure that is automatically provisioned to host that code?",
      "answers": [
        "Elastic Beanstalk",
        "CloudFormation",
        "CloudTrail",
        "CloudFormer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Beanstalk"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "178",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service allows you to run code without having to worry about provisioning any underlying resources (such as virtual machines, databases, etc.)",
      "answers": [
        "EC2",
        "EC2 Container Service",
        "DynamoDB",
        "Lambda"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lambda"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "179",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon's highly scaleable DNS service is known as ________.",
      "answers": [
        "CloudTrail",
        "Directory Service",
        "Elastic Map Reduce",
        "Route 53"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Route 53"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "180",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS compute service is specifically designed to assist you in processing large data sets?",
      "answers": [
        "Big Data Processing",
        "Elasticache",
        "EC2",
        "Elastic Map Reduce"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Map Reduce"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "181",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is the difference between Elastic Beanstalk & CloudFormation?",
      "answers": [
        "Elastic Beanstalk is a monitoring tool to view the performance of your AWS resources, where as CloudFormation is an automated provisioning engine designed to deploy entire cloud environments via a JSON script.",
        "Elastic Beanstalk automatically handles the deployment, from capacity provisioning, load balancing, auto-scaling to application health monitoring based on the code you upload to it, where as CloudFormation is a security service designed to harden your cloud against an attack such as a DDOS",
        "Elastic Beanstalk automatically handles the deployment, from capacity provisioning, load balancing, auto-scaling to application health monitoring based on the code you upload to it, where as CloudFormation is an automated provisioning engine designed to deploy entire cloud environments via a JSON script.",
        "There is no difference between the two. Elastic Beanstalk was simply the code name used internally for CloudFormation, prior to the product being released."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Beanstalk automatically handles the deployment, from capacity provisioning, load balancing, auto-scaling to application health monitoring based on the code you upload to it, where as CloudFormation is an automated provisioning engine designed to deploy entire cloud environments via a JSON script."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "182",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service is used as a CDN to distribute content around the world?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudFormation",
        "CloudStream",
        "CloudFront",
        "CloudPush"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "183",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the following AWS solutions offers durable, available storage for flat files?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis",
        "CloudFront Edge Locations",
        "SQS",
        "S3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "184",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the following AWS services would be the best choice for long term data archival?",
      "answers": [
        "S3",
        "CloudFront",
        "EFS",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glacier"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "185",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service offers the following database engines: SQL, MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Aurora, and Oracle?",
      "answers": [
        "Redshift",
        "DynamoDB",
        "Relational Database Service (RDS)",
        "Kinesis"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Relational Database Service (RDS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "186",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the following AWS services is used primarily for data warehousing?",
      "answers": [
        "Redshift",
        "RDS",
        "DynamoDB",
        "DMS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Redshift"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "187",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service is used for collating large amounts of data streamed from multiple sources?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis",
        "SQS",
        "CloudFront",
        "CloudCapture"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "188",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You need to add users to your AWS account and set password rotation policies for these new users. Which AWS service would best fit your requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Directory Services",
        "Identity Access Management (IAM)",
        "Inspector",
        "Key Management Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Identity Access Management (IAM)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "189",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You need to supply auditors with logs detailing the individual users that provision specific resources on your AWS platform. Which service would best meet this need?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudFormation",
        "CloudTrail",
        "CloudTrailOpsWorks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "190",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You need a configuration management service that enables your system administrators to configure and operate your web applications using Chef. Which AWS service would best suit your needs?",
      "answers": [
        "OpsWorks",
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudFormation",
        "CloudTrail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["OpsWorks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "191",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Your digital media agency needs to convert their media files in to different formats to suit different devices. Which AWS service should you consider using to meet these needs?",
      "answers": [
        "AppStream",
        "SQS",
        "SWF",
        "Elastic Transcoder"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Transcoder"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "192",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which statement best describes IAM",
      "answers": [
        "IAM allows you to manage users, groups, roles, and their corresponding level of access to the AWS Platform.",
        "IAM allows you to manage users passwords only. AWS staff must create new users for your organisation. This is done by raising a ticket.",
        "IAM allows you to manage permissions for AWS resources only.",
        "IAM stands for Improvised Application Management and it allows you to deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["IAM allows you to manage users, groups, roles, and their corresponding level of access to the AWS Platform."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "193",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a feature of IAM?",
      "answers": [
        "Centralised control of your AWS account",
        "Integrates with existing active directory account allowing single sign on",
        "Fine-grained access control to AWS resources",
        "The ability to create User/Group/Roles",
        "Allows you to set up your own password rotation policy",
        "Allows you to setup biometric authentication, so that no passwords are required"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Allows you to setup biometric authentication, so that no passwords are required"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "194",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Power User Access allows ________.",
      "answers": [
        "Full Access to all AWS services and resources",
        "Read Only access to all AWS services and resources",
        "Access to all AWS services except for management of groups and users within IAM",
        "Users to inspect the source code of the AWS platform"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Access to all AWS services except for management of groups and users within IAM"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "195",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What level of access does the 'root' account have?",
      "answers": [
        "Read Only Access",
        "Power User Access",
        "Administrator Access",
        "No Access"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Administrator Access"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "196",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are a solutions architect working for a large engineering company who are moving their existing legacy hardware to AWS. You have configured their first AWS account and you have set up IAM. Your company will be primarily based out of West Germany, however they will have a small subsidiary operating out of South Korea and you will need an AWS environment configured there as well. Which of the following statements is true?",
      "answers": [
        "You will then need to configure Users and Policy Documents for each region respectively.",
        "You will need to configure Users and Policy Documents only once, as these are applied globally.",
        "You will need to configure your users regionally, however your policy documents are global.",
        "You will need to configure your policy documents regionally, however your users are global."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["You will need to configure Users and Policy Documents only once, as these are applied globally."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "197",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You have a client who is considering moving to AWS services and do not yet have an account. What is the first thing the company should do to set up an AWS Account?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an account using Cloud Search.",
        "Set up an account using their company email address.",
        "Set up an account via SQS (Simple Queue Service)",
        "Set up an account via SNS (Simple Notification Service)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up an account using their company email address."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "198",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are a security administrator working for a hotel chain. You have a new member of staff who has started as a systems administrator and they will need full access to the AWS console. You have created the user account and generated the access key id and the secret access key. You have moved this user into the group where the other administrators are and you have provided the new user with their secret access key and their access key id. However when they go to log in to the AWS console, they cannot sign in. What could be the cause of this?",
      "answers": [
        "You have not applied the 'log in from console' policy document to the user. You must apply this first so that they can log in.",
        "Your user is trying to log in from the AWS console from outside the corporate network. This is not possible.",
        "You have not yet activated multi-factor authentication for the user, so by default they will not be able to log in.",
        "You cannot log in to the AWS console using the Access Key ID and Secret Access Key, instead you must generate a password for the user and supply the user with this password, as well as the unique link to sign in to the AWS console."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["You cannot log in to the AWS console using the Access Key ID and Secret Access Key, instead you must generate a password for the user and supply the user with this password, as well as the unique link to sign in to the AWS console."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "199",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is an additional way to secure IAM for both the root login and new users alike?",
      "answers": [
        "Implement multi-factor Authentication for all accounts.",
        "Store the access key id and secret access key of all users in a publically accessible plain text document on S3 of which only you and members of your organisation know the address to.",
        "Configure the AWS console so that you can only log in to it from a specific IP Address range",
        "Configure the AWS console so that you can only log in to it from your internal network IP address range."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement multi-factor Authentication for all accounts."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "200",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default when you create a new user in the IAM console, what level of access do they have?",
      "answers": [
        "Read only access to all AWS services.",
        "No access to all AWS services.",
        "Administrator access to all AWS services.",
        "Power user access to all AWS services"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["No access to all AWS services."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "201",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In what language are policy documents written?",
      "answers": [
        "Node.js",
        "Java",
        "JSON",
        "Python"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["JSON"]
    }
  }
]
